all right how do you know how to camera
I'll try it the best angle is to get it
up here so you got it you should switch
your seat to there so you can get George
steering wheels and thing and I
basically killed it you know good
morning skull peas
[Music]
God we got we got some way where am I
going that way go that way guys we just
did we just did 41 Action News don't
bother watching it no no we're not gonna
say you know the reporters very nice
there's unrealistic expectations around
what self-driving cars are
you know you start out the interview and
this is why we're never really going to
do press demos again at least not until
they are like flawless door-to-door
because this is what people expect right
people don't understand really what a
hard problem is so you just saw what the
car did you saw it take that exit you
saw it no it's not been messing up I'm
for like five minutes and I'm impressed
by this but your average person is not
right it works you in the mirror which
is yeah so we usually we usually switch
the horizonal people have any vendor
completely unrealistic expectation for
what self-driving car technology is for
me
I'm impressed if I do nothing for ten
minutes um they see one mistake and
they're like oh how this thing is
horrifying
of course it's horrifying if you put it
on the road without a person right and I
think Tesla's figured this out this is
what we were talking about like you sit
right here I keep doing this up there
but like if it went for that I call it
pretty good do that exit it was vivillon
did you see that
no but you just have to yo if we ever do
a press demo again we have to script it
so well we have to know and it's just
not worth daily yeah it's really just
not worth doing guys like you know and
you just have so much out of your
control versus I mean these periscopes
like you really see what the technology
is I don't know so I don't know how you
deal with this problem maybe you pay
overpaid Media Consultants you don't
know I'd never do that like they
know wait if I apparently oh I thought
it was gonna off I rebooted then we
thought they'd fix that bug the bug with
the I thought it would show the same
speed but ya know doing doing doing
press is kind of a kind of a bummer
y'all yeah so Eric moraga saying the
self-driving car should be renamed to
enhance cruise control well but okay so
enhanced cruise control is fine but you
know that's not a very splashy marketing
turn right and you can even use the
worst term driver assistance system and
nobody knows what that means right
saying self-driving car triggers the DMV
I mean I kind of love triggering people
we love the DMV we respect their
authority but like triggering them is
just kind of fun
of course you know you can say whatever
you want because this is America we have
the First Amendment Internet all this do
you can really say whatever you want on
the Internet
how do you read these comments when
watching the side no one was watching it
sideways but see I'm super impressed by
Palin - yep
did it do this with her yeah but the
whole frame is right away why can't I
enter my destination why doesn't it work
at red lights like you don't understand
like this is most driving yeah
but I don't know I mean I guess people
don't see the usefulness of a 90
percent self-driving car yeah I'll
certainly not people who like walk to
work and then you know who don't really
drive around and who don't use a car
like majority of people Kansas City
definitely could view it's just
I don't know
what are you doing you got any idea
scobie's scope is what do we do to
better make the public aware aware and
reasonable expectations you know welcome
as sons it's their first day on
periscope that's right you go first days
easy son's son easy son easy Oh easy you
know what's nice we can be out of Kansas
soon enforce a squads name are you
driving - ohm Omaha Nebraska Omaha
Nebraska is a sweet place we're doing
this presentation at the University
Nebraska metropolis is of America that
people don't man we're going to
America's vanilla gorilla house how the
news is going okay okay the reporter
she's very nice
but there is that there is a
communication issue right okay so first
off I mean let's break it to write you
know I'm very honest with you guys I was
you have 41 Action News right so already
what that does is like set up the frame
of stories they can do in Canton we're
like okay let's do 41 Action News you
know there's no way this could be a hit
piece right
unlike Reuters there's a terrible news
organization which lawyers is Reuters is
banned from comma yeah yeah we're like
okay so the frame of this story is
always gonna be it's that's puff pieces
right the problem comes in - you can't
promote something as a as a self-driving
car know you can fix all of this in
editing but then it's then it's fake and
I really don't want it to be fake right
the truth is there's very little news
that exists to actually inform the
public right a news plays on your
emotion it doesn't exist to educate
so this we don't do that on periscope do
I play with your emotion people let's go
play with your emotions they only send
us love family send us the way you've
always been man only that's see but
that's the frame of periscope right you
can talk about the frame of 41 Action
News you can talk about the frame of
periscope right oh well it's always
gonna be some hey you know what I'm
surprised by anytime our gets
posted on Reddit it's nothing but hate
anything our get posted on YouTube
it's nothing but love man news is the
truth is the people who read hacker news
are very distinct for the people who
comment on Hacker News a lot of people
read hacker news and they're generally
the positive people the people who
comment are kind of like though don't
know it's so hard man I got a guy who
could it go good no but I mean it's
particularly true about hacker news
because hacker news you have a lot of
you know you're like are like oh maybe
huh armchair engineers is the word fresh
every time this thing like gets down to
the six minute boss yeah yeah right but
that's also kind of a hard thing to
convey on a short news because the truth
is what this is for is people who are
just driving for like an hour which is
one driving is inherently this
incredibly boring thing when you think
about yourself driving right now
tea for there's no need riving not doing
yeah I wonder how many
the reason you think we're cheating is
because the whole world is cheating
right and there's no penalty for
cheating because truthiness beats truth
now there's only reward for like these
these amazing videos that people make
can sell eight hundred dollar products
no alike then fail we live in a world
today where truthiness is more believed
an actual truth by like truthiness is
the be like first glance believability
we set the bar yeah
sure no man
just when I think I'm thinking last
night that like you know we're about to
have a paradigm shift and realness is
about to come back in you see that and
it's not even it's not even like the
fault of anybody you can't really point
fingers but just just it's a structural
problem
we shouldn't subscribe to their
well right like like don't
again there's really there's no reality
they're just like operating in a world
where certain stories can spread you
could talk about that a lot with outrage
to Danny right Lea it's hard to even
attribute malice outrage just happens to
be a more viral emotion than well why do
people watch the news finally watching
action 41 news anyway at least like you
know you're always hoping morning shows
are certainly better than like like the
five o'clock news at 7 o'clock
news 5 o'clock news did you know about
these 7 things in your household that
can kill you make sure you tune in after
this commercial break
yeah Arby's need bacon cheeseburgers
they're not one of the seven things that
can kill you but to be honest you know
and they're talking about like yeah this
woman had a stove fall on her then she
dies watch out for stoves they're in
your house if your stove buckled to the
wall this man
watch out for bacon cheeseburgers
they're actually more likely to kill you
right now it's actually like it will
kill you car accidents yep my few young
I'll actually just once I'm a 27 year
old white male 28 28 my number one risk
of death is suicide
followed by truck overdose a car
accident almost in Missouri I think we
saw the Welcome Center we've been are we
burn alive Kansas we talk about through
Kansas is fun last night nice space
I just just structurally don't know what
to do yes
by the way interesting to go back when
Tesla fares autopilot and see what did
they do right did they just sell it to
the people who are buying the cars and
they were like you can also get this and
you know it's an upgrade of your driving
no I remember the early marketing or we
gonna talk about that wasn't a minute
but first time I want to say that this
sign is brought to you by Dan Carlin's
common sense Dan Carlin has this great
show he also makes this on their podcast
hardcore history that's really listen to
this you know a lot of this sort of like
it really really helps teach you how to
think just know what testa did for
autopilot was they announced it they
didn't really talk about what it was I
think like I fit in the car with
autopilot is this and you watch these
videos and to be honest so so so so so
talking with the reporter this morning
she said like you know test autopilot is
way better and the reason she probably
thinks that um is because she used test
autopilot on a stretch of road like this
with different expectations right so
we've been driving for for like 25
minutes now and I've done nothing
but when you're in a 41 Action News
segment and you're trying to get a shot
it's a different it's a different frame
guys reverse engineer everything
reverses
the people that that know that it's
better they they get we don't we don't
need to hype it up to people that aren't
feelings it's not even really better
look it's the identical things no no no
I mean I'm better than what comes on
there right people buy something that
the people like in action for doing news
but not buy the stock I wouldn't even
say that right it's not II no disrespect
to action for anyone they probably would
they probably would right but they
wouldn't like think of it in the same
sort of class right
and maybe this is our fault for calling
it a self-driving car right we're
driving better than that you know I see
trucks do that and I don't know whether
to blame the truck driver or like the
wind has the wind it might be I mean
I've never driven a truck and a 90s
asking what state is this Missouri oh
we've been in Missouri the whole when do
we get to Nebraska y'all absolutely show
is the show-me state Kansas or Missouri
show me what
like the slogans if the live free or die
for camp it's Kansas
- what's Missouri slogan oh it's
Missouri because the Rogen is literally
it's Missouri no no it's Missouri slogan
the show me oh the show okay so what's
Kansas we got a lot of prairies and like
single oil rigs on the side of the road
that's so many of those
city great song
wait is there at a Kansas City Oklahoma
no no but oh no oh oh isn't there
another musicals guys have bummed out
too small and a nineties areas
show-me-state any Chicago up States its
I'm not bummed about how the press one I
don't care about that the world is
reliving it right but no it's that we
live in a world that is completely
incapable of thinking critically
all right I mean like like like like
like this is not think through this
problem on a high level and think about
I mean it's okay there's a saying in the
media right the second you're actually
educated on a subject you realize what
the media that's right but you
look at the media talking about like say
say you know about life you know say
you're your pilot you know that air but
it's right you look at the media talk
about pilots and airplanes you're like
wow they have no idea what they're
talking about yet these same people
still trust the media on other issues
like artificial intelligence right that
I don't know maybe the media knows but
people are not like people don't think
like wow I'm a pilot I know they're
on pilots why do you not think
they're also on artificial
intelligence or things like that right
it's a structural problem
that's what's bumming me out
maybe it is better with things like
youtube and periscope I mean you
actually can kind of see the truth yes
maybe the world is going in a better
direction but then you have you know
sites like Facebook which maybe Facebook
starts out as you know you're seeing
updates with your friends on newsfeed
but now it's your single Busby's right
you're seeing like that people who
have figured out how to game new meaning
the systems are exploitable and like the
exploit for the system that I'm talking
about is kind of like the truthiness is
better than truth
and I don't
and like on any platform you could start
out with this very truthful guys I want
I want to scope is right now see look at
messed up we were honest about it right
scope is I want you all to hold me
accountable if I ever be called
I know I know I won't listen
and that's see it concerns me right but
do people grow up thinking I want to be
when I grow up
oh my god have you seen what
blog is like hearing of these people oh
my god and this is why we can't do the
ico hi guys we were gonna do an ICL but
we can't do it because cryptos full of
immature idiots who want to be crypto
rich don't ruin a community right
[Music]
Yeah right like you can't you know
Bitcoin starts out as this really fight
for like liberation and truth right I
mean this is the same complain I you
know you have about like Punk's right
and everyone is still a real punk is
probably complaining about this saying
like punk became a brand we literally
tried to be anti brands guys is really
bummed yeah
oh no man I wanna be weak you would feel
like if if someone else has built this
this and this
hard to like put yourself in that
position but I would have technical
criticisms at the points
but then you know if you talk to me
about like the machine learning and talk
to me about like what's involved I'll be
like yeah I think we can do better but
like I get that it takes to be honest I
don't know I thought I could sell I
didn't think I could actually solve elon
division problem in the formulas what he
asked for was basically a replacement of
mobilize IQ 3 and that I thought that I
could actually do but I mean hello we
have pool lanes a holistic path
predictor and a lead car predictor it's
what do you think we got those ideas
right there are obvious ideas yeah it's
you know as what was asked me in the
Tesla contract right you know finally
now we're talking about how to move to
new architecture
happiness stick respect
I think you'd be more do you be more
harsh than you oh no and I would
absolutely be harsh right but it's it
but it's even beyond being harsh it's
like
yeah I know no you see this is like I
might be harsh for the first like couple
minutes yeah but then I think I'm the
type of person who you can sit down and
have a conversation with and I'll like
you know I do want to know
yeah but Scooby's who are watching we
use our system for the first time like
what were you thinking were you guys in
the first moments that you used it
after drinking
no one's used it
the part that says no very impressed
famous how many think a lot of people I
guess they had looks like they should
say it's not even that right it
realistic and it's also that they were
like they drove the car before the
system for long periods of time and then
they put the system in and they're like
and maybe they even tried this toxin but
to be fair like there is no stop Lane
keep assist on the toilet yeah but you
can still have adaptive retinol Breville
said he tried it that's exactly of
course like I believe that the people
who actually understand especially the
people who build it certainly feel that
yeah right but this is the whole yes way
better than what Honda and there's this
dangerous really is like anything in the
world know what 1% of people make all
our food like you do but where we can
get growth from
oh I don't know that I don't know about
you can't have all this like lack of
necessity for things and massive saying
like it's so we shouldn't do it
I'm saying it's and we should
recognize that it's and then do
it anyway because we're hey man what are
we doing little like that's just me
is so expensive groaning what the hoodie
is so expensive you know what you know
what an honor that guy when we get home
we're double in the prize ability good
positions give you two 49 to 49 it's a
little less to dump no but seriously
though buddy's going up to 249 two pies
in honor in honor of the world being
we're gonna update on the
hoodie page buddy in honor of the world
being it's now 249 weekly and
travefy on your phone bitch up says I
cancel my Tesla P hundred D order to get
a car I can run come on your pace and
lack of BS is good right like yeah I
mean there's people
it's just not most of the worlds but you
can't like make people appreciate
something that they don't know
yeah no we'll do it we'll do it in the
new year in the new year don't let me
don't let me forget scope is 40 years
hoodies are going up yeah you're a
couple you remind me guys okay I'm
trying an experiment in January I'm
buying a fat suit
well then I'm gonna wear it around right
but if I like I buy a suit that adds
like 3040 pounds to my body I'm gonna
get ripped
just by pacing George paces he pieces
throughout the day get like 10,000 steps
just as we should periscope
transparently off yeah it's like the
real
that's always think of as given to the I
see how the pen opticon foundation yeah
Jamaican jewel says can I sell my own
counterfeit hoodies for a much lower
price
no that's trademark infringement we have
a trademark on the comma off we're
gonna sue you sue you
I love suing people I've lawyers will
sue you to be honest if you sold
knockoff hoodies if it entertains me I
would let them stay if you put it this
way if you did it as a joke I'm totally
fine with it and tried to like seriously
make money doing it you were serious
about it you like suing Tandon 19
says we're gone
we're gonna go to you event and I
believe that it's gonna be hot chocolate
that's the word on the street and maybe
some
I'm not sure yeah
you know Mila likes like like lets
people use attacks and screamin I like
that if you don't take the world
seriously choose her you take that
seriously
what the tractor couldn't see we have
Chicago stuff
throws what do you need to stop for you
a tourist right here or the Paris got
many people Oh got 57 good a lot of you
guys like 60 so spread the word about
truth right
values reven said there's cookies coffee
reven coffee the Akamai really kind
people that's how expand issue sensing
is anyone working on open pilot for semi
truth is that the band question cuz
we've gotten that alone oh that's so far
though that's not a car you said I don't
drive a semi truck I build ship for me
like a big yeah yeah they have a
different connector though
they have a notch in the obd of semi
trucks so then you don't plug he said
that well that is good yeah don't plug a
panda but someone should make it twelve
a 24 volt to 12 volt and after that be
cool we can make 24 volt pandas for
$10,000 of penalties
yeah and if you can play another price
and stuff yeah that's right yeah breven
seven seven ease our 24 volt no but
seriously so if you bought it at the
beginning you actually got to yeah
because it was the medium large size now
you get one and then hoodies are about
to double in price I love it right like
those people who have hoodies man that's
an appreciation getting really getting
early on hoodie coin hoodies are not a
security that you got past how we test
they have a functional use people bought
hoodies for many other reasons I had an
expectation of profit
what to do about the world how are we
gonna educate people when the people who
claim to be educated or the biggest
scammers in history
no one wants you to really be educated
educator
you say this right and like like I mean
this isn't like this is almost like like
the fantasy of make America great again
right like it's I'm not sure people were
ever better the same oceans and I really
think it's the same like you
know you had people back in the day
selling like snake oil elixir down here
yeah these people are a little bored
maybe evil it and you like find out some
hard facts of Wikipedia don't use
Facebook download the Wikipedia app
today you can find you can find news
that supports literally whatever like
not even whatever opinion you have but
whatever truth and studies studies
like did you guys know you can't get a
speeding ticket if you're behind a car
that's playing faster than someone said
I want to buy the full set Panna draft
and the neon and the hoodie for 250 but
I need a support we don't do or no
support there's no support just let me
tell you seriously when you send an
email to support we give you to support
choices right support choice 1 it's open
source fix it yourself support choice to
send it back for a full refund I'm not
like oh so on someone sent a support
question they sent like educate yourself
yeah like the camera always has like a
kind of halo effect at the lens you
don't see it on most cell phone cameras
because they're correcting for the
software a we get ad set that's right
yes so it is vegan and it's spelled like
big
so to get exact directions on what to do
[Music]
get home yeah okay you don't know how to
like these like read code this is not
for you we appreciate your business
don't we honestly like almost all like
we don't appreciate your business but
like if you want to buy okay so whatever
safe right I was saying and saying I
want to say it's keep hacking a leak
right um if people first hear that
they're like I'll keep adding believe
and you want to only want to keep
hacking confined to the elite few people
know keep hacking elite me and recognize
that hacking is an elite skill that
anyone can learn but only a few people
have afraid in order to get the skilled
you have to put in time and learn it
it's the same thing with this right like
self-driving is insurance and this is
something that is really lost like a
fast and everywhere argos talking about
the community support though this great
community look like you don't start are
you willing to put in time in alright
well this isn't for you
like look it'll get easier and to be
honest was probably gonna happen
longer term with combat AI is somebody
else is gonna figure out how to package
our deal with consumers
I'm here to actually try to change right
you don't change the world if you just
like keep it on the same trajectory but
faster right you're not you're not like
like changing your course I wouldn't be
changing anything if I you know sped up
to 90 on this highway right you change
what is in faucet nobody knows he's ever
been there
just look nobody's ever taken that road
before the rav4 is gonna be on one of
those driving back no yeah this Bergen
do that every car looks the same now no
pilot go go go yon engage go go go smoky
one says wait aggressively
Wiki FM radio said could you ask George
about the time complexity of lord floyd
marsh lloyd marshals out o floyd
warshall that's that's great so that's
complete graph traversal I think that's
like Dijkstra from all the paths naively
off the top of my head I think okay so
the floyd-warshall is is Dijkstra it's
like it's like pre solving Dijkstra
right so Dijkstra is given two nodes in
a graph what's the shortest path between
them
so if your graph has three vertices
nice V Square D or just like n cubed if
you're kind of like like just o event
cubes
I think it's B squared you know social
foot marshal solves Dijkstra for all
events I can think about this a little
bit more right so you want to know
basically the shortest path between any
two vertices in a graph and the graph is
can have wings
I'm pretty sure floyd-warshall is three
loops inside of each other I have
written it before this is the downside
of being allowed to use the internet
during competition programming we would
use the internet during common
programming practice and then we'd go to
the actual competitions
if you have an excuse it would like flip
through Bing algorithms that you bring
like you trying concrete and stuff that
you can print stuff out too so you print
out I'm sure I'm sure you'd literally
have a floyd-warshall implementation
they are ready to go you just kind of
shove it in but yeah okay so let's see
what you do
so Oh God even if you ask me about the
complexity of Dijkstra I have to think
it through these are not things that I
know off the top of my head but the
truth is you don't want to know
okay
you want to be able to think things
through but you have to have some basic
so let's go over a little bit of basics
do you guys know like what a graph is
yeah Tomiko he said Oh
be cute Oh a beat cubed okay it's b
cubed all right all right all right so I
had I was close to the order of
magnitude but for some reason it's not
squared and the number of edges
apparently until
yeah I mean okay you could see kind of
intuitively why that's true right
because I can't imagine like a complete
graph taking I can take it true I could
I can free derived yeah any more any
more concise questions
Marcia Mason no we're not let's let's
derive it let's figure out why it's okay
so you you remember you have a graph so
a graph is what I say a graph you know I
don't mean like a times I know so a
graph has like vertices and edges of a
great you have like like to think of
like a point and then like edges when a
graph is like a structures when they
talk about graph theory it's not about
you know what yeah yeah because you
could graph y equals MX plus D but no I
mean something other than that right all
right so let's redirect like Martian
so first off let's figure out the time
complexity of times two so if you have a
grand frightened think about traversing
your graph as you're trying to get from
this think about okay here's a sample so
I think it's very relevant to spur on a
road trip think about each city like a
vertex right
and each road connecting them as an edge
and then each edge has has like a cost
right so there's a cost to traversing
that right so you might think of costs
as like timings right so we're taking
the highway from Kansas City which is
one vertex to Omaha which is another
vertex and this maybe has a cost of you
know it's it's it's let's say 180
because it's a hundred eighty minutes
right we could also stop by you know
whatever like like rubber or faucet yeah
right
faucets maybe this edge over here right
and maybe it takes you know 300 minutes
to get from faucet to Omaha and then 100
minutes to from Kansas City over you
could take this path in the graph for a
total of 400 or you can take this path
for 180 right so if you're routing
Dijkstra it's the thing that I just
should know off the top of my head but I
don't it's been a while you want to
figure out what's the shortest path from
point A to point B so the way that you
yes
you think of a star a star works if you
have a silver stick for any stars just
Dykstra Dykstra is a star without a
currency from trying to heuristic
function you can think I was kind of
like
an estimate for how close you want write
an estimate so say you got to say you've
got to false it right and you say there
was like a lot of nodes between Fawcett
and Omaha you wouldn't necessarily know
your distance from Fawcett to Omaha off
the top of your head without actually
traversing a right so the algorithm is
you started a vertex you expand out all
of the intimus right then you go to
another vertex and you expand out all of
the edges as well you go to another
vertex yeah so you're going to each
vertex once and Dijkstra so you think
about the complexity as V and then
you're traversing each edge at most once
right because the trick is what you get
from here to here you don't have to save
all the slower intermediate this one day
passes you only have to save the fastest
driver so space complexity is one number
per vertex and the time complexity is
the number of vertices times a number of
edges all right you can think about why
because the most you'll ever have to do
is traverse each edge ones and visit
each node in the graph once in order to
get to and right
is VD right so if Floyd Marshall is vq
that means you're doing something in the
time complexity of the number of
vertices ma cute
okay you know what I mean yeah okay all
right you can see why this is obviously
true because originally I said it was V
squared eat but you're not gonna have to
traverse edges
unless they are shorter because your
computing every pass right you can think
about imagine pre-computing Dijkstra for
the whole graph right between every
vertex and every other vertex
so that's naively V Square D right
because if Dijkstra's Vee will that's
one vertex to one other but then one
vertex to vertex did every vertex is
also V D it doesn't matter that there's
one target because it might be the last
one to explore to be honest there isn't
even a space complexity difference you
have to say if you have to say although
just following us there's my there's my
there's my there's my computer science
lecture for the day right you're gonna
end up now you do have to safe weather
so if you're doing Dijkstra you're gonna
end up saving so if you're trying to get
from point A to point B right you're
going to know that path well but at all
the intermediates you're gonna save the
shortest distance from that intermediate
to point A yeah maybe cuz eventually
eventually one of your intermediates
will be one hop away from point B and
then you can get a total of total path
we get them said thank you sis
Neela okay it's a log V right so I'm
thinking about that now watch I was
thinking it had to be less than me right
but but but I don't see naively why
so so so
yeah and there's another version of it
that's me squared to give to I think I
took a graph theory course for a little
bit yeah you guys all get the advantage
of being able to
by Mary
okay so you can pick it up maybe that is
the now versus out okay you can think
about putting things in a in a that's
all god I have to write a proof for why
it's not ve but you can think about but
a vague heuristic function to getcha to
get
and you want to start by your at point a
right you expand out this edge has a
weight of 20 this edge has a weight of
10 and such as a way to 5 write it so if
the first one you're gonna want to
expand out is the one with a way of 5
because you're trying to find the
shortest path and then from the way to 5
right if this one has if it only has
like one edge away from it the weight of
30 then you're gonna want to revisit the
one with a weight of 10 right you're
gonna want to keep them sorted you're
gonna want to keep them sorted like that
right
so if that's the data structure you're
using you'll have to prove to me that
like some vertices will never be
so let's think of some examples
this is obvious
okay okay so you can think about
Dijkstra from from point A to point B
and you have like a really really long
graph right like say like it's ten notes
all right say there's just literally one
straight line and you're just proceeding
along that you're obviously gonna have
to visit every vertex but that
complexity is already covered in the
edges so that would actually be just go
of e right because if there's one vertex
between each right so now let's think
about the opposite example which is a
completely a complete graph is a graph
where every vertex is connected to every
other vertex every edge is possible
graph but how many edges are possible on
the graph
every vertex is gonna every vertex is
connected to every other vertex
well what about a complete graph was
business was one one with one how many
edges are possible
what I would know no one wears the oil I
have one no right in and assume that
it's a normal graph so one node one node
and just one note how many edges can
know it there are no edges because you
can't do that particularly well so now
you have two notes how many I just can
have they have dreams 3 3 now you have 4
nodes
harder
what is it that's like a sentence it was
just and spare - sit down squared - 1 no
words so let's let's look at the first
one how many edges does it
yes first one is three so good 2 1 3 2 1
right yeah so it's like you have to read
minus 1 that word for 5 well no so it's
4 2 n minus 3 plus 2 plus 1 so it's so
it's so it's the N minus 1 but expand it
out
so like n minus 1 times n minus 2 over 2
is just n minus 1 times a minus 2
is it fact or okay what's effective work
respect Oriole is that you oh yeah
so when there's five there's like four
plus three plus two
5cf where + 3 + 2 + 1 so 5 is
really what you do is you type zero one
three six ten into the online
encyclopedia of integer sequences and it
tells you exactly what that is right and
times and times n plus one over two yeah
that sounds my evening right well so
let's see so so let's say four five six
and five was
oh it is 10% so 5 times 5 minus 1 there
you go
magic the magic of Google see this is
why nobody ever had to think anymore
just google it unless you actually
derive that in your house which was good
for you and if you ended if you actually
derived it at your house without paper
that done you beat us look like he
copied pasted it from it was in like
some logic no no derived it in his head
and then wrote it up in logic will give
the scope use the benefit of a doubt how
long does a real computer science
lecture oh this is how to think about
you know someone say I surely understand
self-driving a reinforcement learning
problem supervised door ok topic all
been to machine learning yeah so ok you
think about it very naively and it's
obvious it's a supervised learning
problem right so given a picture what
did the human do in this picture
so that's supervised learning because
you have your X's which are the pictures
and your Y's which are what the human to
hit and you want to learn a function f
of x equals y
to drive a car if it was that simple our
car would work way way way better than
it does but it's not that because in a
supervised learning like the typical
scenario the one the academics always
write out you make this assumption that
your data is iid independent and
identically distributed what this means
is that every data point is independent
of every other data point you can think
of like when this will be true like if I
am like sampling without sampling with
replacement right like if I have a bingo
table right and I pull out one number
and then I put that number back in the
table and spin it again and pick out
another number right those two events
are completely independent events are
two coin flips or independent events
right but if I'm sampling like without
replacement if I take that ball out well
then the next event depends on what
happened in the first event we think
about drawing cards from a deck of cards
right if I'm holding two aces in my hand
that affects the probability that the
next card that I'm going to draw is nice
unless you're a cheater and you filled
your deck aces
I'm so that's what independent means and
identically distributed means that any
sample of the data looks like any other
sample of the data under any statistical
test as this goes out to infinity right
so this is again true about like
questions right but on where might this
not be true if you think about like
predicting the next letter in Wikipedia
right
your data is not an industry because if
the article is about bananas I mean the
word fruit is likely is more likely show
up right so that's actually dependent on
your context right supervised learning
makes these two assumptions independent
identically distributed so now let's
talk about whether these examples
actually apply to self-driving cars is
one frame independent of an expert
if there's a car in front of me in this
frame does that affect the probability
of there being a car in front of me in
the hax frame yeah so you violate your
independence assumption there
how about identically distributed right
yeah well
yeah I mean you have to talk about
identically distributed under like what
model yeah but um so so the real way
that this stuff is violated is it's so
you can say okay well I'll shuffle up
all the data and they'll be enough of it
and then it's int and then actually is
iid but the problem is that isn't what
happens from the rope on the road you're
executing your model like sequentially
right and you have your output of the
model actually affects what the next
state looks right if the thing you told
the car to turn left in the next frame
it's likely to be further to the left
which is the whole reason that
self-driving cars weren't honest
so in the literature this is referred to
as behavioural cloning or cascading
errors
and some things a reinforcement learning
fixes this reinforcement learning fixes
this B costs so one little bit would fix
this if we could train it as a minor in
a simulator if you're actually letting
the model act then you don't have this
problem but when we're testing it on the
data that you guys sent to us we can't
let them on lacked because what actually
happened is what happens
kind of like the lost theory of contract
she had Jessica submit dinner
oh can we test the simulator that
perfectly mimics the real world
not perfectly
a little business but again you're only
testing some we're not training in
salmon you could train a simulator to
build a simulator is kind of like part
and coding the self-driving car it's
graphics instead of vision but still
yeah therefore the half a semester I
took this course until it's gone for my
market to say hey Kerry
I wouldn't like it is
like it is gonna be real people
so wiki at that radio who asked you the
question before what does George's
favorite language to program
- I thought your big rust man Oh God
just like the shill for nice to show for
us and then let other people try to code
in it you know what they say Minh if
you're good it doesn't matter how shitty
your tools are but if you have good
tools or even better
happy add two cups of coffee this
morning three yeah I drink your coffee
to help solve the simulator problem okay
so what you're you can read our paper
I'm learning a driving simulator games
are kind of the answer just really hard
to get to work well you could be right
next to that tree that's like your best
option Amazonia
oh really in the middle of no we in the
window yes maybe we're in the middle of
nowhere here in Nebraska things that we
would have seen a sign
what's the nebraska motto
yeah go grab it you out there
so tomorrow
yeah so my talk today is gonna be a lot
of complaining about the lack of
realness in the world but I'll try to
refrain from talking at colleges about
how college is the greatest game in this
day I'll try I'll try to refrain but
guys it really is the Kris Kim mystery
would you look when you look at the
wealth that has been extracted from our
nation's youth we're still in Missouri
yeah when I was like pretty far down and
Nebraska I gotta go
what time is the event I think that 2
p.m. or shoo
are we streaming the event well stream a
bit from the presentations we attic and
I hopefully like if I'm standing by
podium
yeah yo you know we got Obama to come
speak intense it was real pissed at a
podium yeah you know I was like DEFCON
lips yes I spoke about crypto kitties I
made some serious cash off crypto
Katie's either believe in true realness
or complete if you haven't
realized it's not true just enjoyable
thing about crypto kitties is it is real
and honest because we pretend to be
something else right it's not like
they're talking about crypto kitties how
they help the underprivileged you
they're just cats on a blockchain man
why I'm trade em sell a collection right
like they're not trying to be something
that they're not
yeah it's hypocrisy that's the problem
right because if you live in a world
where everything has to be rational and
true what kind of a boring world is
right but we could live in a world where
everything is at least honest yeah
Oh Previn is trying to set up a live a
YouTube live you do block like Google
but don't even think about Facebook live
it's friends don't let friends use
Facebook I'll play with the focus now is
there been no bridges to give you a
sorry
Missouri is there show-me-state just
don't show me a pretty feminin country
about 16 you're like what happened
don't take me home country
take me home country I think it's
literally the country roads that he was
taking those country roads no do it you
can definitely be there what do you
think that's far with highway though
yeah I agree I'm good
okay y'all what's your blast
it's a muscle let's go George exercise
work it out yeah
one way to anything guys go make the
turn make the turn look it down your
eyes Nebraska motto is one news if you
need more footage we got that right
there take a nap
the Nebraska motto is see the problem is
okay so here's the problem
I have an interview if you guys want to
look it up ND t TV where i shelf for
bagels oh yeah where my hair is bleached
blonde I just want a CT app they pulled
my friend to the side and they're like I
swear I get high a lot but I wasn't
right the difference attack and defense
insecure right when you attack you
always win because if you don't exploit
anything nobody knows about you if you
do you're a winner
right will you defend you always loose
because say you fix nine out of the ten
exploits you still get grilled for the
one unit so complete
the problem is I view self-driving cars
like an attack and I think like if it
makes that turn it's a success right
versus the defend which is if it ever
makes a mistake over I think attack is a
much more exciting way to view the world
right eventually you want to attack and
then we have some people like
self-driving cars with no real order to
look at the zero those people are
literally sentencing thousands of people
to die Africa right if you could build
something that's twice as safe as people
you save 15,000 live but we shouldn't
even save 15,000 lives until we can save
30,000 and you kind of stop hearing
people say that that's so funny you guys
be idiots on our self-driving cars and
we're giving a or like Volvo's
already shipping a level 4 system in in
2017 yeah you know what they pushed it
to 2021 which is another word for never
it's not even soon TM we're gonna call
that never TM and now they're shipping a
level 2 system to people to get them
comfortable with it they're shipping
Volvo Drive pilot which is here
them to open violent
it was like if we could flick stop it
with the PR spin
sometimes because were harder than we
anticipated
and I pee in my own city guys Stockport
seems more like oh really
before you get to Nebraska I'm gonna go
there oh forget there will you pick the
gas station be good
no unweighted that's heard about the
gallon scam right let me talk about the
gallons go to gallon challenge yeah it
turns out when this car says it's out of
gas it actually has like two gallons
left in the gas tank it's really good
we've lost so much time slowing we're
like now yesterday you are old to try
ghosts and this Clark Kent coast yeah in
old cars but it's Eddie you're actually
out of gas
you know I feel like I'm going fast
right truthiness is better than truth
okay we're all doomed
gas stations about 15 minutes
I get to be 15 minutes away deal
see you've been time of peace but now I
have to pee well Oh excellent now we all
have to stop good now it's now I don't
anyti I'll pick you guys up later but I
want to get a coffee so then I will
happen oh let's get more calm down
yeah
our periscope I'm sick of holding you
but there's a wrench coming up sponsor
today sponsored tested I want anyone any
let's leave the scope little by Scottie
[Music]